<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<database xmlns="http://www.good_food.com">
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="XSLFile1.xsl"?>
	
<!--List of food recipes with description separated by ID-->
	
  <food food_id="ID1">
    <name>Farm stand chicken chef’s salad</name>
    <overall_score>7</overall_score>
    <ingredients>tre
      <ingredient_name>2 boneless skinless chicken thighs, poached and shredded</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>2 tablespoons homemade mayonnaise</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1 teaspoon chopped fresh oregano</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/4 teaspoon kosher salt</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>pinch of cracked black pepper</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1 small garlic clove, minced</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1 cup shredded mustard greens</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/2 cup shredded cabbage</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/2 cup julienned carrots</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/4 cup julienned Applegate Farm Provolone Cheese</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/4 cup julienned Applegate Farm Honey Ham</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1 tablespoon olive oil</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1 teaspoon apple cider vinegar</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/4 teaspoon organic sugar</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>1/8 teaspoon salt</ingredient_name>
      <ingredient_name>lemon wedges (optional)</ingredient_name>
    </ingredients>
	  <tags>health</tags>
    <description>Introducing the Farm Stand Chicken Chef's Salad – a vibrant and satisfying salad that combines the best of farm-fresh ingredients.
	With tender grilled chicken, crisp greens, colorful vegetables, creamy avocado, tangy feta cheese, and a zesty lemon herb dressing, 
	this salad is a burst of flavors that will leave you craving more. Get ready to indulge in a healthy and delicious culinary experience!</description>
  </food>

	<food food_id="ID2">
		<name>Sweet potato and peanut curry</name>
		<overall_score>8</overall_score>
		<ingredients>
			<ingredient_name>1 tbsp coconut oil</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1 onion, chopped</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>2 garlic cloves, grated</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>thumb-sized piece ginger, grated</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>3 tbsp Thai red curry paste (check the label to make sure it’s vegetarian/ vegan)</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1 tbsp smooth peanut butter</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>500g sweet potato, peeled and cut into chunks</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>400ml can coconut milk</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>200g bag spinach</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1 lime, juiced</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>cooked rice, to serve (optional)</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>dry roasted peanuts, to serve (optional)</ingredient_name>
		</ingredients>
		<tags>vegetarian</tags>
		<description>
			I'm excited to share with you a delicious and aromatic recipe for Sweet Potato and Peanut Curry. 
			This vibrant dish combines the natural sweetness of sweet potatoes with the nutty richness of peanuts, creating a truly delightful culinary experience. 
			The creamy coconut milk adds a velvety texture, while the blend of aromatic spices elevates the flavors to new heights. 
			Whether you're a fan of spicy dishes or simply looking to explore new tastes, this curry is bound to satisfy your cravings. 
			So, let's dive into this mouthwatering recipe and get ready to indulge in a symphony of flavors!
		</description>
	</food>

	<food food_id="ID3">
		<name>Easy huevos rancheros</name>
		<overall_score>10</overall_score>
		<ingredients>
			<ingredient_name>1 tbsp vegetable oil or sunflower oil</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1 corn tortilla wrap</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1 egg</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>200g can black beans, drained</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>juice 1/2 lime</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>1/2 ripe avocado, peeled and sliced</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>50g feta, crumbled</ingredient_name>
			<ingredient_name>hot chilli sauce (we like sriracha)</ingredient_name>
		</ingredients>
		<tags>vegetarian</tags>
		<description>
			An easy Mexican breakfast that'll keep you going all morning, 
			this huevos rancheros recipe (aka 'ranch eggs') is packed with vibrant colours and flavours.
		</description>
	</food>
	
<!--List of customer info and his orders-->
	
	<customers_orders>
		<customer_email>custemail1@gmail.com</customer_email>
		<customer_phone>01 23 45 67 89</customer_phone>
		<customer_fname>Albert</customer_fname>
		<customer_lname>Smith</customer_lname>
		<customer_adress>Adress1</customer_adress>
		<order_date>2024-01-01T01:01:01+03:00</order_date>
	  
		<order number="1">
		  <food_id>ID1</food_id>
		</order>
	  
		<order number="3">
		  <food_id>ID3</food_id>
		</order>
	</customers_orders>

	<customers_orders>
		<customer_email>custemail2@gmail.com</customer_email>
		<customer_phone>98 76 54 32 10</customer_phone>
		<customer_fname>Rita</customer_fname>
		<customer_lname>Ora</customer_lname>
		<customer_adress>Adress2</customer_adress>
		<order_date>2024-11-02T01:01:01+03:00</order_date>

		<order number="1">
			<food_id>ID2</food_id>
		</order>

		<order number="2">
			<food_id>ID1</food_id>
		</order>
	</customers_orders>
	
<!--List of reviews separated by ID-->	

  <reviews FoodID ="ID1">
    <customer_review>
      <customer_email>email1@gmail.com</customer_email>
      <comment>
		  The Farm Stand Chicken Chef's Salad is a true delight for the taste buds. 
	  The fresh, crunchy vegetables paired with tender grilled chicken and flavorful bacon create a harmonious blend of flavors and textures. 
	  The portion size is generous, making it a satisfying and wholesome meal option. 
	  The dressing is light and complements the ingredients perfectly. 
	  Overall, this salad is a delicious and refreshing choice for a light yet filling meal. 
	  Highly recommended for anyone looking for a tasty and nutritious salad option!
	  </comment>
      <given_score>7</given_score>
    </customer_review>
	  
    <customer_review>
      <customer_email>email2@gmail.com</customer_email>
      <comment>A solid choice for those looking for a healthy and filling salad option</comment>
      <given_score>7</given_score>
    </customer_review>
	  
  </reviews>

	<reviews FoodID ="ID2">
		<customer_review>
			<customer_email>email1@gmail.com</customer_email>
			<comment>
				Prepare to have your taste buds dazzled! 
				The Sweet Potato and Peanut Curry is a culinary masterpiece that effortlessly blends sweet, savory, and spicy flavors in perfect harmony. 
				The tender sweet potatoes provide a delightful sweetness that pairs beautifully with the nutty richness of the peanuts. 
				The aromatic blend of spices adds depth and complexity to the dish, while the creamy coconut milk creates a luscious and velvety texture. 
				Every bite is a burst of flavors that will keep you coming back for more. 
				Whether you're a fan of curries or looking for a vegetarian-friendly option, this dish is a winner. 
				It's a true crowd-pleaser that will leave you craving seconds and sharing the recipe with everyone you know. 
				Don't miss out on this delightful culinary adventure!
			</comment>
			<given_score>8</given_score>
		</customer_review>
	</reviews>

	<reviews FoodID ="ID3">
		<customer_review>
			<customer_email>email2@gmail.com</customer_email>
			<comment>
				Say hello to breakfast perfection! 
				The Easy Huevos Rancheros recipe is a quick and simple way to start your day with a burst of Mexican flavors. 
				This dish combines perfectly fried eggs with a zesty tomato-based salsa, all served on a crispy tortilla. 
				It's a deliciously satisfying breakfast that will leave you energized and ready to conquer the day. 
				With minimal effort and maximum flavor, this recipe is a must-try for anyone looking to spice up their morning routine. 
				Get ready to savor every bite of this mouthwatering breakfast delight!
			</comment>
			<given_score>10</given_score>
		</customer_review>
	</reviews>
	
</database>